Tufts Daily UP029
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Daily
1980 -- 2021
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
UP029
72 Linear Feet
25 Volumes
3812 Digital Object(s)
1 Web sites
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into series by year beginning with 1980, in addition to having a series devoted to web crawls.
Biographical / Historical
The Tufts Daily, founded in 1980, is the daily undergraduate student newspaper for Tufts University. Its mission is to provide a source of news for the Tufts community, a forum for the exchange of ideas, and a means for students to gain experience in journalism. It covers university news, sports, and events as well as some national and international news. It also includes editorials, a calendar of events, and syndicated comics. Published and distributed free of charge on class days during the academic year, the Tufts Daily is student-run and receives no financial support from Tufts University.
Particularly valuable are the Tufts Daily photographs documenting campus life - the people, places, events, and activities of Tufts University.
Related Materials
UP057, Today Tufts, DCA
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of the Tufts Daily, the daily, student-run newspaper of Tufts University. The Tufts Daily covers university news, sports, and events as well as national and international news taken from wire services. It also includes editorials, announcements and calendar items of events (primarily on the Medford campus), and nationally syndicated comics.
Each volume covers one semester, except for volume 7, which includes the entire calendar year 1983. Individual issues are often mis-labeled on the masthead. The mistakes can include incorrect volume, number or date statements. Issues until Spring 1994 are bound. Reference copies are available in the Archives reading room. A headline index is available electronically (from 1985) and in a card file (from 1980) in the archives reading room.
The collection also includes web crawls of the paper's web site.
Content Warning
This finding aid contains language that may be offensive or outdated. Because such language is in titles or direct transcription of published materials, it has not been changed. Keeping this language intact provides the most accurate depiction of the creators' intent, and can potentially tell us important things about bigotry and bias on the part of the creators, or in a particular historical context. It can also preserve terms formerly applied by a group to self-identify that have since fallen out of common usage. For more information on DCA's content warning policy please visit our website.
Student Activities -- Student Publishing; University history; Student life
- Web crawls, 2015 -- 2021; UP029.000; 1 Web sites
  Scope and Contents
  Quarterly web crawls of the Tufts Daily website crawled by DCA, as part of the Student Organizations web collection, to document the presesence of Tufts University student organizations on the web.
  Other Finding Aids
  To see all of websites crawled as part of the Student Organizations web collection, please visit https://archive-it.org/collections/6387
  - Tufts Daily, 2015 -- 2021; UP029.000.00001
    Conditions Governing Access
    Open for research.
    General
    Frequency: daily crawl.
- Tufts Daily back issues, 1994 -- 2005; UP029-001 (Box 1)
- Tufts Daily back issues, 2002; UP029-002 (Box 2)
- Tufts Daily back issues, 2003 -- 2004; UP029-003 (Box 3)
- Tufts Daily back issues, 2000 -- 2002; UP029-004 (Box 4)
- Tufts Daily, 1980; UP029.001; 1.2 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes; 101 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains issues of the Tufts Daily, the student newspaper of Tufts University.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 February 25; UP029.001.001.00001 (Volume 1)
    Volume, issue
    1, 1
    newspapers
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 February 28; UP029.001.001.00002 (Volume 1)
    1, 4
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 March 12; UP029.001.001.00003 (Volume 1)
    1, 8
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 March 19; UP029.001.001.00004 (Volume 1)
    1, 13
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 March 24; UP029.001.001.00005 (Volume 1)
    1, 16
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 March 25; UP029.001.001.00006 (Volume 1)
    1, 17
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 April 10; UP029.001.001.00007 (Volume 1)
    1, 25
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 April 16; UP029.001.001.00008 (Volume 1)
    1, 29
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 April 28; UP029.001.001.00009 (Volume 1)
    1, 35
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 September 04; UP029.001.001.00010 (Volume 1)
    2, 1
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 September 10; UP029.001.001.00011 (Volume 1)
    2, 2
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 September 15; UP029.001.001.00012 (Volume 1)
    2, 5
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 September 17; UP029.001.001.00013 (Volume 1)
    2, 7
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 September 26; UP029.001.001.00014 (Volume 1)
    2, 14
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 September 29; UP029.001.001.00015 (Volume 1)
    2, 15
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 01; UP029.001.001.00016 (Volume 1)
    2, 17
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 15; UP029.001.001.00017 (Volume 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 23; UP029.001.001.00018 (Volume 1)
    2, 31
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 24; UP029.001.001.00019 (Volume 1)
    2, 32
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 November 03; UP029.001.001.00020 (Volume 1)
    2, 37
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 November 05; UP029.001.001.00021 (Volume 1)
    2, 39
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 November 06; UP029.001.001.00022 (Volume 1)
    2, 40
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 November 10; UP029.001.001.00023 (Volume 1)
    2, 42
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 November 14; UP029.001.001.00024 (Volume 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 November 17; UP029.001.001.00025 (Volume 1)
    2, 46
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 November 18; UP029.001.001.00026 (Volume 1)
    2, 47
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 November 25; UP029.001.001.00027 (Volume 1)
    2, 52
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 November 26; UP029.001.001.00028 (Volume 1)
    2, 53
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 December 05; UP029.001.001.00029 (Volume 1)
    2, 57
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 December 09; UP029.001.001.00030 (Volume 1)
    2, 59
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 February 26; UP029.001.045.00001 (Volume 45)
    1, 2
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 February 27; UP029.001.045.00002 (Volume 45)
    1, 3
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 February 29; UP029.001.045.00003 (Volume 45)
    1, 5
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 March 10; UP029.001.045.00004 (Volume 45)
    1, 6
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 March 11; UP029.001.045.00005 (Volume 45)
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 March 13; UP029.001.045.00006 (Volume 45)
    1, 9
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 March 14; UP029.001.045.00007 (Volume 45)
    1, 10
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 March 17; UP029.001.045.00008 (Volume 45)
    1, 11
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 March 18; UP029.001.045.00009 (Volume 45)
    1, 12
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 March 20; UP029.001.045.00010 (Volume 45)
    1, 14
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 March 21; UP029.001.045.00011 (Volume 45)
    1, 15
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 March 26; UP029.001.045.00012 (Volume 45)
    1, 18
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 March 27; UP029.001.045.00013 (Volume 45)
    1, 19
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 March 28; UP029.001.045.00014 (Volume 45)
    1, 20
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 March 31; UP029.001.045.00015 (Volume 45)
    1, 21
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 April 01; UP029.001.045.00016 (Volume 45)
    1, 22
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 April 08; UP029.001.045.00017 (Volume 45)
    1, 23
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 April 09; UP029.001.045.00018 (Volume 45)
    1, 24
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 April 11; UP029.001.045.00019 (Volume 45)
    1, 26
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 April 14; UP029.001.045.00020 (Volume 45)
    1, 27
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 April 15; UP029.001.045.00021 (Volume 45)
    1, 28
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 April 17; UP029.001.045.00022 (Volume 45)
    1, 30
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 April 18; UP029.001.045.00023 (Volume 45)
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 April 23; UP029.001.045.00024 (Volume 45)
    1, 32
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 April 24; UP029.001.045.00025 (Volume 45)
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 April 25; UP029.001.045.00026 (Volume 45)
    1, 34
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 April 29; UP029.001.045.00027 (Volume 45)
    1, 36
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 April 30; UP029.001.045.00028 (Volume 45)
    1, 37
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 May 01; UP029.001.045.00029 (Volume 45)
    1, 38
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 May 02; UP029.001.045.00030 (Volume 45)
    1, 39
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 September 11; UP029.001.045.00031 (Volume 45)
    2, 3
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 September 12; UP029.001.045.00032 (Volume 45)
    2, 4
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 September 16; UP029.001.045.00033 (Volume 45)
    2, 6
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 September 18; UP029.001.045.00034 (Volume 45)
    2, 8
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 September 19; UP029.001.045.00035 (Volume 45)
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 September 22; UP029.001.045.00036 (Volume 45)
    2, 10
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 September 23; UP029.001.045.00037 (Volume 45)
    2, 11
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 September 24; UP029.001.045.00038 (Volume 45)
    2, 12
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 September 25; UP029.001.045.00039 (Volume 45)
    2, 13
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 September 30; UP029.001.045.00040 (Volume 45)
    2, 16
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 03; UP029.001.045.00041 (Volume 45)
    2, 18
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 06; UP029.001.045.00042 (Volume 45)
    2, 19
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 07; UP029.001.045.00043 (Volume 45)
    2, 20
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 08; UP029.001.045.00044 (Volume 45)
    2, 21
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 09; UP029.001.045.00045 (Volume 45)
    2, 22
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 10; UP029.001.045.00046 (Volume 45)
    2, 23
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 14; UP029.001.045.00047 (Volume 45)
    2, 24
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 16; UP029.001.045.00048 (Volume 45)
    2, 26
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 17; UP029.001.045.00049 (Volume 45)
    2, 27
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 20; UP029.001.045.00050 (Volume 45)
    2, 28
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 21; UP029.001.045.00051 (Volume 45)
    2, 29
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 22; UP029.001.045.00052 (Volume 45)
    2, 30
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 27; UP029.001.045.00053 (Volume 45)
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 28; UP029.001.045.00054 (Volume 45)
    2, 33
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 29; UP029.001.045.00055 (Volume 45)
    2, 34
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 30; UP029.001.045.00056 (Volume 45)
    2, 35
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 October 31; UP029.001.045.00057 (Volume 45)
    2, 36
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 November 04; UP029.001.045.00058 (Volume 45)
    2, 38
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 November 07; UP029.001.045.00059 (Volume 45)
    2, 41
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 November 12; UP029.001.045.00060 (Volume 45)
    2, 43
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 November 13; UP029.001.045.00061 (Volume 45)
    2, 44
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 November 19; UP029.001.045.00062 (Volume 45)
    2, 48
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 November 20; UP029.001.045.00063 (Volume 45)
    2, 49
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 November 21; UP029.001.045.00064 (Volume 45)
    2, 50
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 November 24; UP029.001.045.00065 (Volume 45)
    2, 51
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 December 02; UP029.001.045.00066 (Volume 45)
    2, 54
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 December 03; UP029.001.045.00067 (Volume 45)
    2, 55
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 December 04; UP029.001.045.00068 (Volume 45)
    2, 56
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 December 08; UP029.001.045.00069 (Volume 45)
    2, 58
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 December 10; UP029.001.045.00070 (Volume 45)
    2, 60
  - Tufts Daily, 1980 December 11; UP029.001.045.00071 (Volume 45)
    2, 61
- Tufts Daily, 1981; UP029.002; 1.2 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes; 125 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 January 29; UP029.002.002.00001 (Volume 2)
    3, 2
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 January 30; UP029.002.002.00002 (Volume 2)
    3, 3
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 February 02; UP029.002.002.00003 (Volume 2)
    3, 4
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 February 04; UP029.002.002.00004 (Volume 2)
    3, 6
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 February 09; UP029.002.002.00005 (Volume 2)
    3, 9
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 February 10; UP029.002.002.00006 (Volume 2)
    3, 10
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 February 11; UP029.002.002.00007 (Volume 2)
    3, 11
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 February 12; UP029.002.002.00008 (Volume 2)
    3, 12
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 February 17; UP029.002.002.00009 (Volume 2)
    3, 14
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 February 18; UP029.002.002.00010 (Volume 2)
    3, 15
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 February 19; UP029.002.002.00011 (Volume 2)
    3, 16
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 February 20; UP029.002.002.00012 (Volume 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 February 23; UP029.002.002.00013 (Volume 2)
    3, 17
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 February 24; UP029.002.002.00014 (Volume 2)
    3, 19
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 February 25; UP029.002.002.00015 (Volume 2)
    3, 20
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 February 26; UP029.002.002.00016 (Volume 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 February 27; UP029.002.002.00017 (Volume 2)
    3, 21
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 March 02; UP029.002.002.00018 (Volume 2)
    3, 22
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 March 03; UP029.002.002.00019 (Volume 2)
    3, 23
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 March 04; UP029.002.002.00020 (Volume 2)
    3, 24
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 March 05; UP029.002.002.00021 (Volume 2)
    3, 25
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 March 06; UP029.002.002.00022 (Volume 2)
    3, 26
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 March 09; UP029.002.002.00023 (Volume 2)
    3, 27
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 March 11; UP029.002.002.00024 (Volume 2)
    3, 29
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 March 12; UP029.002.002.00025 (Volume 2)
    3, 30
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 March 13; UP029.002.002.00026 (Volume 2)
    3, 31
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 March 16; UP029.002.002.00027 (Volume 2)
    3, 32
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 March 17; UP029.002.002.00028 (Volume 2)
    3, 33
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 March 18; UP029.002.002.00029 (Volume 2)
    3, 34
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 March 19; UP029.002.002.00030 (Volume 2)
    3, 35
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 March 20; UP029.002.002.00031 (Volume 2)
    3, 36
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 March 30; UP029.002.002.00032 (Volume 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 March 31; UP029.002.002.00033 (Volume 2)
    3, 37
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 01; UP029.002.002.00034 (Volume 2)
    3, 38
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 01; UP029.002.002.00035 (Volume 2)
    April Fool's Day issue
    3, 39
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 01; UP029.002.002.00036 (Volume 2)
    April Fool's Day issue, different from item 35.
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 02; UP029.002.002.00037 (Volume 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 03; UP029.002.002.00038 (Volume 2)
    3, 41
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 06; UP029.002.002.00039 (Volume 2)
    3, 42
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 07; UP029.002.002.00040 (Volume 2)
    3, 43
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 08; UP029.002.002.00041 (Volume 2)
    3, 44
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 09; UP029.002.002.00042 (Volume 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 10; UP029.002.002.00043 (Volume 2)
    3, 46
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 13; UP029.002.002.00044 (Volume 2)
    3, 47
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 14; UP029.002.002.00045 (Volume 2)
    3, 48
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 15; UP029.002.002.00046 (Volume 2)
    3, 50
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 21; UP029.002.002.00047 (Volume 2)
    3, 51
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 22; UP029.002.002.00048 (Volume 2)
    3, 52
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 23; UP029.002.002.00049 (Volume 2)
    3, 53
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 24; UP029.002.002.00050 (Volume 2)
    3, 54
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 28; UP029.002.002.00051 (Volume 2)
    3, 56
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 29; UP029.002.002.00052 (Volume 2)
    3, 57
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 30; UP029.002.002.00053 (Volume 2)
    3, 58
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 May 01; UP029.002.002.00054 (Volume 2)
    3, 59
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 May 04; UP029.002.002.00055 (Volume 2)
    3, 60
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 May 05; UP029.002.002.00056 (Volume 2)
    3, 61
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 May 06; UP029.002.002.00057 (Volume 2)
    3, 62
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 May 07; UP029.002.002.00058 (Volume 2)
    3, 63
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 May 08; UP029.002.002.00059 (Volume 2)
    3, 64
  - Tufts Daily, Commencement Issue, 1981; UP029.002.002.00060 (Volume 2)
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 September 03; UP029.002.002.00061 (Volume 2)
    4, 1
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 September 17; UP029.002.002.00062 (Volume 2)
    4, 8
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 September 22; UP029.002.002.00063 (Volume 2)
    4, 11
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 September 25; UP029.002.002.00064 (Volume 2)
    4, 14
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 September 28; UP029.002.002.00065 (Volume 2)
    4, 15
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 September 30; UP029.002.002.00066 (Volume 2)
    4, 17
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 October 01; UP029.002.002.00067 (Volume 2)
    4, 18
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 October 02; UP029.002.002.00068 (Volume 2)
    4, 19
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 October 05; UP029.002.002.00069 (Volume 2)
    4, 20
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 October 07; UP029.002.002.00070 (Volume 2)
    4, 22
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 November 20; UP029.002.002.00071 (Volume 2)
    4, 50
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 November 23; UP029.002.002.00072 (Volume 2)
    4, 51
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 November 25; UP029.002.002.00073 (Volume 2)
    4, 53
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 December 04; UP029.002.002.00074 (Volume 2)
    4, 57
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 December 07; UP029.002.002.00075 (Volume 2)
    4, 58
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 December 09; UP029.002.002.00076 (Volume 2)
    4, 60
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 December 10; UP029.002.002.00077 (Volume 2)
    4, 61
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 December 11; UP029.002.002.00078 (Volume 2)
    4, 62
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 January 26; UP029.002.044.00001 (Volume 44)
    3, 1
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 February 03; UP029.002.044.00002 (Volume 44)
    3, 5
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 February 05; UP029.002.044.00003 (Volume 44)
    3, 7
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 February 06; UP029.002.044.00004 (Volume 44)
    3, 8
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 February 13; UP029.002.044.00005 (Volume 44)
    3, 13
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 March 10; UP029.002.044.00006 (Volume 44)
    3, 28
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 April 27; UP029.002.044.00007 (Volume 44)
    3, 55
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 September 06; UP029.002.044.00008 (Volume 44)
    4, 6
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 September 09; UP029.002.044.00009 (Volume 44)
    4, 2
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 September 10; UP029.002.044.00010 (Volume 44)
    4, 3
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 September 11; UP029.002.044.00011 (Volume 44)
    4, 4
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 September 14; UP029.002.044.00012 (Volume 44)
    4, 5
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 September 15; UP029.002.044.00013 (Volume 44)
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 September 17; UP029.002.044.00014 (Volume 44)
    4, 7
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 September 21; UP029.002.044.00015 (Volume 44)
    4, 10
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 September 23; UP029.002.044.00016 (Volume 44)
    4, 12
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 September 29; UP029.002.044.00017 (Volume 44)
    4, 16
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 October 06; UP029.002.044.00018 (Volume 44)
    4, 21
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 October 13; UP029.002.044.00019 (Volume 44)
    4, 23
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 October 14; UP029.002.044.00020 (Volume 44)
    4, 24
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 October 15; UP029.002.044.00021 (Volume 44)
    4, 25
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 October 16; UP029.002.044.00022 (Volume 44)
    4, 26
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 October 19; UP029.002.044.00023 (Volume 44)
    4, 27
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 October 20; UP029.002.044.00024 (Volume 44)
    4, 28
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 October 21; UP029.002.044.00025 (Volume 44)
    4, 29
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 October 22; UP029.002.044.00026 (Volume 44)
    4, 30
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 October 28; UP029.002.044.00027 (Volume 44)
    4, 33
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 October 29; UP029.002.044.00028 (Volume 44)
    4, 34
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 November 02; UP029.002.044.00029 (Volume 44)
    4, 36
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 November 03; UP029.002.044.00030 (Volume 44)
    4, 37
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 November 04; UP029.002.044.00031 (Volume 44)
    4, 38
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 November 05; UP029.002.044.00032 (Volume 44)
    4, 39
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 November 06; UP029.002.044.00033 (Volume 44)
    4, 40
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 November 09; UP029.002.044.00034 (Volume 44)
    4, 41
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 November 11; UP029.002.044.00035 (Volume 44)
    40, 43
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 November 12; UP029.002.044.00036 (Volume 44)
    4, 44
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 November 13; UP029.002.044.00037 (Volume 44)
    4, 45
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 November 16; UP029.002.044.00038 (Volume 44)
    4, 46
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 November 17; UP029.002.044.00039 (Volume 44)
    4, 47
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 November 18; UP029.002.044.00040 (Volume 44)
    4, 48
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 November 19; UP029.002.044.00041 (Volume 44)
    4, 49
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 November 24; UP029.002.044.00042 (Volume 44)
    4, 52
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 December 01; UP029.002.044.00043 (Volume 44)
    4, 54
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 December 02; UP029.002.044.00044 (Volume 44)
    4, 55
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 December 03; UP029.002.044.00045 (Volume 44)
    4, 56
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 December 08; UP029.002.044.00046 (Volume 44)
    4, 59
  - Tufts Daily, 1981 October 27; UP029.002.DO.00001
    4, 32
- Tufts Daily, 1982 -- 1983; UP029.003; 2.4 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes; 125 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 January 27; UP029.003.003.00001 (Volume 3)
    5, 2
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 February 05; UP029.003.003.00002 (Volume 3)
    5, 7
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 February 08; UP029.003.003.00003 (Volume 3)
    5, 8
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 February 09; UP029.003.003.00004 (Volume 3)
    5, 9
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 February 10; UP029.003.003.00005 (Volume 3)
    5, 10
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 February 12; UP029.003.003.00006 (Volume 3)
    5, 12
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 February 18; UP029.003.003.00007 (Volume 3)
    5, 15
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 February 19; UP029.003.003.00008 (Volume 3)
    5, 16
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 February 24; UP029.003.003.00009 (Volume 3)
    5, 19
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 February 25; UP029.003.003.00010 (Volume 3)
    5, 20
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 February 26; UP029.003.003.00011 (Volume 3)
    5, 26
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 March 01; UP029.003.003.00012 (Volume 3)
    5, 22
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 March 02; UP029.003.003.00013 (Volume 3)
    5, 23
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 March 03; UP029.003.003.00014 (Volume 3)
    5, 24
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 March 09; UP029.003.003.00015 (Volume 3)
    5, 28
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 March 11; UP029.003.003.00016 (Volume 3)
    5, 30
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 April 14; UP029.003.003.00017 (Volume 3)
    5, 43
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 April 16; UP029.003.003.00018 (Volume 3)
    5, 45
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 April 23; UP029.003.003.00019 (Volume 3)
    5, 49
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 April 28; UP029.003.003.00020 (Volume 3)
    5, 52
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 May 05; UP029.003.003.00021 (Volume 3)
    5, 57
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 May 06; UP029.003.003.00022 (Volume 3)
    5, 58
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 September 08; UP029.003.003.00023 (Volume 3)
    6, 1
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 September 20; UP029.003.003.00024 (Volume 3)
    6, 9
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 September 28; UP029.003.003.00025 (Volume 3)
    6, 14
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 October 08; UP029.003.003.00026 (Volume 3)
    6, 22
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 October 14; UP029.003.003.00027 (Volume 3)
    6, 25
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 October 22; UP029.003.003.00028 (Volume 3)
    6, 31
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 November 16; UP029.003.003.00029 (Volume 3)
    6, 48
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 November 17; UP029.003.003.00030 (Volume 3)
    6, 49
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 November 19; UP029.003.003.00031 (Volume 3)
    6, 51
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 November 24; UP029.003.003.00032 (Volume 3)
    6, 54
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 November 29; UP029.003.003.00033 (Volume 3)
    6, 55
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 December 02; UP029.003.003.00034 (Volume 3)
    6, 58
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 December 06; UP029.003.003.00035 (Volume 3)
    6, 60
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 September 09; UP029.003.042.00001 (Volume 42)
    6, 2
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 September 10; UP029.003.042.00002 (Volume 42)
    6, 3
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 September 13; UP029.003.042.00003 (Volume 42)
    6, 4
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 September 14; UP029.003.042.00004 (Volume 42)
    6, 5
  - Tufts Daily, 1982 September 15; UP029.003.042.00005 (Volume 42)
    6, 6